wordunscrambler.me 2019-05-12

# Privacy Policy - WordUnscrambler.me

The privacy of our visitors, here at **wordunscrambler.me** is very important to us.

This page clearly outlines the types of personal information collected and recorded when you visit and use our website. Why do we collect certain information and how we safeguard and use that information. 

## General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)

We are a Data Controller of your information.

wordunscrambler.me legal basis for collecting and using the personal information described in this Privacy Policy depends on the Personal Information we collect and the specific context in which we collect the information:

  * wordunscrambler.me needs to perform a contract with you
  * You have given wordunscrambler.me permission to do so
  * Processing your personal information is in wordunscrambler.me legitimate interests
  * wordunscrambler.me needs to comply with the law

wordunscrambler.me will retain your personal information only for as long as is necessary for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy. We will retain and use your information to the extent necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our policies.

If you are a resident of the European Economic Area (EEA), you have certain data protection rights. If you wish to be informed what Personal Information we hold about you and if you want it to be removed from our systems, please contact us. 

In certain circumstances, you have the following data protection rights:

  * The right to access, update or to delete the information we have on you.
  * The right of rectification.
  * The right to object.
  * The right of restriction.
  * The right to data portability
  * The right to withdraw consent

## Log Files

wordunscrambler.me follows a standard procedure of using log files. These files log visitors when they visit websites. All hosting companies do this and a part of hosting service's analytics. 

The information collected by log files include - 

  * IP(Internet Protocol) Address
  * ISP (Internet Service Provider)
  * Web Browser type
  * Your visit time 
  * date and time stamp
  * referring/exit pages

These are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. The purpose of the information is for analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking user's movement on the website, and gathering demographic information.

## Cookies & Web Beacons

Like any other website, wordunscrambler.me uses 'cookies'. These cookies are used to store information including visitor's preferences, and the pages on the website that the visitor accessed or visited. The information is used to optimize the user's experience by customizing our web page content based on visitor's browser type and/or other information.

  * Google Analytics - For Analytics
  * Twitter, Facebook, Google Plus, YouTube - For social interaction

### Google DoubleClick DART Cookie

Google is one of a third-party vendor on our site. It also uses cookies, known as DART cookies, to serve ads to our site visitors based upon their visit to www.website.com and other sites on the internet. However, visitors may choose to decline the use of DART cookies by visiting the Google ad and content network Privacy Policy at the following URL – <https://policies.google.com/technologies/ads>

You could opt out of personalized ads and control how google show you ads by visiting this page : [https://adssettings.google.com](https://adssettings.google.com/) and <http://www.aboutads.info/choices/>. 

### Our Advertising Partners

Some of advertisers (listed on our ads.txt ) on our site may use cookies and web beacons. Some of our major advertising partners are listed below. Each of our advertising partners has their own Privacy Policy for their policies on user data. For easier access, we hyperlinked to their Privacy Policies below.

  * Google - <https://policies.google.com/technologies/ads>
  * Amazon - <https://www.amazon.com/gp/help/customer/display.html?nodeId=468496>
  * Sovrn - <https://www.sovrn.com/privacy-policy/>
  * DistrictM - <https://districtm.net/en/page/platforms-data-and-privacy-policy/>
  * Index Exchange - <https://www.indexexchange.com/privacy/>
  * AppNexus - <https://www.appnexus.com/platform-privacy-policy>
  * OpenX - <https://www.openx.com/legal/privacy-policy/>
  * Rubicon Project - <https://rubiconproject.com/privacy-policy/>
  * Pubmatic - <https://pubmatic.com/legal/privacy-policy/>

Third-party ad servers or ad networks uses technologies like cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons that are used in their respective advertisements and links that appear on wordunscrambler.me, which are sent directly to users' browser. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. These technologies are used to measure the effectiveness of their advertising campaigns and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see on websites that you visit.

Note that wordunscrambler.me has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

**You can choose to disable or turn off our cookies or third party cookies in your browser settings, However this can affect the usability of our website, and other websites as well.**

 **

## Children's Information

Another part of our priority is adding protection for children while using the internet. We encourage parents and guardians to observe, participate in, and/or monitor and guide their online activity.

wordunscrambler.me does not knowingly collect any Personal Identifiable Information from children under the age of 13. If you think that your child provided this kind of information on our website, we strongly encourage you to contact us immediately and we will do our best efforts to promptly remove such information from our records.

## Consent

By using our website, you hereby consent to our Privacy Policy and agree to its terms.

Updated on 16 Feb 2019

**
